Tucker Larrabee

Richmond, VA 23235 (804) 516-9034 tuckerlarrabee13@gmail.com

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/tuckerlarrabee/ github.com/tuckerlarrabee

PROFILE

Full-stack web developer utilizing functional, agile, and SDLC knowledge from 5 years of experience as a Business Analyst for multiple Insurtech software suite providers. Recently earned certificate in full stack web development from the University of Richmond, with skills in HTML5/CSS3, JavaScript, Node.js, Express.js, React.js, and responsive web design.

TECHNICAL COMPETENCIES

Libraries/Frameworks: **Tools:** Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript ¡Query, Bootstrap, Handlebars, Jest, Heroku, Git, GitHub, Node.js, NPM, Express, React, Bulma MySQL, MongoDB, AWS

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development Certificate

University of Richmond

11/2021 - 05/2022

Bachelor of Science, Insurance & Risk Management

University of South Carolina - Darla Moore School of Business

08/2013 - 05/2017

PROJECTS

CryptoHub | Full-Stack: MongoDB Express React Node Heroku

Project Manager and Javascript Developer (2 Person Team) | https://cryptohubproject.herokuapp.com/

- An aesthetically pleasing Full-Stack application allowing users to create personalized accounts based on the cryptocurrencies they want to follow
- Utilized the user's session to authguard certain screens

Music You May Like | Front End: HTML CSS JavaScript Bulma Git

Project Manager and JavaScript Developer (3 Person Team) | https://tuckerlarrabee.github.io/Music-You-May-Like/

- Implemented multiple third-party APIs to build an application that provides related musical artists/bands based on the user's search
- Utilized Bulma framework for streamlined styling of front-end

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Trilogy Education

06/2022 - present

Web Development Tutor

SpeedBuilder Systems

09/2020 - present | Richmond, VA

Business Analyst

- Led two successful initiatives to integrate 3rd party payment vendors with current platform to facilitate one-time and recurring EFT transactions
- Owned all quality assurance testing around payment vendor integrations, including utilizing FTP servers, manual building of xml payment files, and controlling timed event processes
- Reduced policy non-pay cancellations by roughly 15% as a result of newly introduced EFT auto-pay functionality made possible by the 3rd party payment vendor integrations
- Created technical document around payment vendor configuration dependencies to prevent configuration overlapping

Capgemini Consultant

07/2017 - 09/2020 | Columbia, SC

- Performed root cause analysis for Duck Creek billing defects such as but not limited to outstanding balance discrepancies, erroneous invoice amounts, and missing endorsements via database analysis (SQL) as well as efforts to recreate within the user interface
- Facilitated urgent defect resolution by working through entire process of Software Development Life Cycle, including elicitation of desired system behavior, conveyance of functional requirements to technical team, and creation and execution of test cases